(Howard:)if my mom could've
arranged a carpool.
(Raj:)Oh, yeah?
(Raj:)Well, I've been taking
Pilates class at the rec center,
(Raj:)and my abs look like
sections of a Hershey bar.
(Howard:)Oh, yeah? Won't matter,
you're going down!
(Raj:)No, uh-uh, you're going down!
(Howard:)If anybody's going to go down,
it's going to be you.
(Leonard:)Fellas. It's been 30 minutes.
Nobody's touched each other.
(Sheldon:)I'm glad you decided to reject
your animal hindbrain
(Sheldon:)and return to the
realm of pure intellect.
(Amy:)As am I.
(Amy:)What are you doing?
(Amy:)An experiment.
(Amy:)Nope. Nothing.
Never mind.
(Raj:)You realize you can't win.
(Howard:)I prefer to think
that I can't lose.
(Raj:)You're wrong.
(Raj:)It's only a matter of time
(Raj:)before you fall into
Rat-Man's rat trap.
(Howard:)You pathetic fool!
(Howard:)If there were a rat-catcher,
wouldn't it catch Rat-Man?
(Raj:)Just because I didn't
express myself well
(Raj:)doesn't mean my
underlying point was invalid!
(Raj:)You bloviating buffoon!
(Howard:)You narcissistic nincompoop!
(Raj:)You crimson coward!
(Raj:)Oh, Leonard, wake up,
(Raj:)you're missing some very
excellent superhero quips.